A Guide to the Harold P. Fabian papers FA071
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Snake River Land Company, 1927-1943; 1; 10 Cubic Feet 25 document cases
  - Land Acquisition - Woodward - Parcel 14 - B-42-115, 1929, 1936 (Box 17, Folder 162)
  - Land Acquisition - Riniker - Parcel 15 - 16-42-115 and 39-43-115, 1928 (Box 17, Folder 163)
  - Land Acquisition - Newbold - Parcel 16 - 1-42-116, 1928-1930, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 164)
  - Land Acquisition - Nipper - Parcel 17 - 2-42-116, 1928, 1933-1934 (Box 17, Folder 165)
  - Land Acquisition - Gray - Parcel 20 - 3, A, 4, 5-42-116, 1928-1940 (Box 18, Folder 166)
  - Land Acquisition - Gray - Parcel 20a - A-40-116, Wiel Encroachment, 1938-1944 (Box 18, Folder 167)
  - Land Acquisition - Wilson - Parcel 21 - 16-42-116, 1928-1930, 1942 (Box 18, Folder 168)
  - Land Acquisition - Beagle - Parcel 22 - 17-42-116, 1931-1932, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 169)
  - Land Acquisition - Haight - Parcel 23 - 20-42-116, 1929-1930 (Box 18, Folder 170)
  - Land Acquisition - Miller - Parcel 24 - 31-42-116, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 171)
  - Land Acquisition - Sophia Kelly - Parcel 22-24a - -42-115, 1929-1930 (Box 18, Folder 172)
  - Land Acquisition - McBride - Parcel 25 - 32-42-116, 1928, 1930, 1938 (Box 18, Folder 173)
  - Land Acquisition - Burton - Parcel 26 - 33-42-116, 1928, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 174)
  - Land Acquisition - Jones - Parcel 27 - 35-42-116, 1929-1930 (Box 18, Folder 175)
  - Land Acquisition - Hopson - Parcel 28 - 34, 36-42-116, 1928, 1931-1938 (Box 18, Folder 176)
  - Land Acquisition - Loomis (Van Vleck, Hansen) - Parcel 29 and 29a - 37-42-116, 1928-1929, 1934, 1940-1942, 1944-1945 (Box 18, Folder 177)
  - Land Acquisition - Barber - Parcel 30 - 38-42-116, 1930 (Box 18, Folder 178)
  - Land Acquisition - J. P. Ranch - Parcel 31 - 34 and 37-42-115 and 55 and 56-42-116, 1928-1930 (Box 18, Folder 179)
  - Land Acquisition - J. P. Ranch - Parcel 31 - 34 and 37-42-115 and 55 and 56-42-116, 1931-1936, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 180)
  - Land Acquisition - J. P. Ranch - Parcel 31 - 34 and 37-42-115 and 55 and 56-42-116, 1900-1933 (Box 19, Folder 181)
  - Land Acquisition - Curtis - Parcel 32 - H-42-116, 1929-1932, 1934 (Box 19, Folder 182)
  - Land Acquisition - J. Y. Ranch - Parcel 33 - 8, 12 and G-42-116, 1901-1934, 1938, 1940, 1942, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 183)
  - Land Acquisition - J. Y. Ranch - Parcel 33 - 8, 12 and G-42-116, 1901-1934, 1938, 1940, 1942, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 184)
  - Land Acquisition - Holland - Parcel 34 - 1-43-115 and 4-44-115, 1929-1930 (Box 19, Folder 185)
  - Land Acquisition - Corse - Parcel 36 - 3, 5, and 7-43-116, 1929-1934, 1940 (Box 20, Folder 186)
  - Land Acquisition - Bar BC Ranch (Burt, Corse) - Parcel 36a - 2-43-115, 1929-1930, 1932, 1934-1936, 1938-1940 (Box 20, Folder 187)
  - Land Acquisition - Burt - Parcel 36b - 4-45-114, 1928-1930 (Box 20, Folder 188)
  - Land Acquisition - Kent - Parcel 37 - 4-43-115, 1929 (Box 20, Folder 189)
  - Land Acquisition - Shawback - Parcel 38 - 10-43-115, 1931 (Box 20, Folder 190)
  - Land Acquisition - Chambers (Box 20, Folder 191)
    Parcel 39 - 12-43-115, 1928 Parcel 39a - 4-42-115, 1930
  - Land Acquisition - Riniker - Parcel 40 - 13-43-115, 1928 (Box 20, Folder 192)
  - Land Acquisition - Winger - Parcel 41 - 19-43-115, 1928 (Box 20, Folder 193)
  - Land Acquisition - Redmond - Parcel 42 - 16, D-43-115, 1928-1929, 1933 (Box 20, Folder 194)
  - Land Acquisition - McInelly - Parcel 43 - 27-43-115, 1928 (Box 20, Folder 195)
  - Land Acquisition - Ireton - Parcel 44 - 28-43-115, 1928, 1932, 1934, 1936-1937 (Box 20, Folder 196)
  - Land Acquisition - Menor - Parcel 45 - 32-43-115 and 20-43-116, 1928-1929, 1934, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 197)
  - Land Acquisition - Smith - Parcel 46 - 33-43-115 and 21-43-116, 1930-1932, 1934, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 198)
  - Land Acquisition - Chambers - Parcel 47 - 34-43-115, 1928, 1930 (Box 20, Folder 199)
  - Land Acquisition - Shinkle - Parcel 49 - 48-43-115, 1928-1929, 1933-1934, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 200)
  - Land Acquisition - Kafferlin - Parcel 50 - 53-43-115, 1930, 1932, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 201)
  - Land Acquisition - Budge - Parcel 51 - 54-43-115, 1931 (Box 20, Folder 202)
  - Land Acquisition - Hoagland - Parcel 52 - I-43-115, 1929-1930 (Box 20, Folder 203)
  - Land Acquisition - Gibo - Parcel 53 - 2-43-116, 1929-1930, 1933, 1940 (Box 20, Folder 204)
  - Land Acquisition - Elbo Ranch - Parcel 54 (P182) - 3, 4, 5-43-116, 1929-1930, 1932 (Box 20, Folder 205)
  - Land Acquisition - Horel - Parcel 55 - 6-43-116, 1928-1930 (Box 20, Folder 206)
  - Land Acquisition - Ferry Ranch - Parcel 56 - 9 and 23-43-116, 1929-1930, 1932, 1934, 1937, 1940 (Box 20, Folder 207)
  - Land Acquisition - Ward - Parcel 58 - 11-43-116, 1929-1930 (Box 20, Folder 208)
  - Land Acquisition - Brown - Parcel 59 - 14-43-116, 1929-1930 (Box 20, Folder 209)
  - Land Acquisition - Altenreid - Parcel 60 - 18-43-116, 1929-1930 (Box 20, Folder 210)
  - Land Acquisition - Harris - Parcel 61 - 22-43-116, 1930, 1932-1933 (Box 21, Folder 211)
  - Land Acquisition - Bayse - Parcel 62 - 26-43-116, 1928, 1934 (Box 21, Folder 212)
  - Land Acquisition - Manges - Parcel 63 - D-43-116, 1929-1930 (Box 21, Folder 213)
  - Land Acquisition - McCabe - Parcel 64 - G-43-116, 1929-1930 (Box 21, Folder 214)
  - Land Acquisition - Ford - Parcel 65 - 2-44-113, 1928, 1930 (Box 21, Folder 215)
  - Land Acquisition - Webb - Parcel 66 - 3-44-113, 1928-1929, 1930 (Box 21, Folder 216)
  - Land Acquisition - Ferrin - Parcel 67 - A-44-113, D-45-113 and L-44-114, 1929-1930 (Box 21, Folder 217)
  - Land Acquisition - Ferrin - Parcel 68 - 1-44-113 and 1-44-114, 1929-1930, 1932-1933 (Box 21, Folder 218)
  - Land Acquisition - Fugar [Fuger] - Parcel 69 - 2-44-114, 1930-1932 (Box 21, Folder 219)
  - Land Acquisition - Ferrin - Parcel 70 - 3, 6-8, 15 and 16-44-114, 1927-1938 (Box 21, Folder 220)
  - Land Acquisition - Ferrin - Parcel 70 - 3, 6-8, 15 and 16-44-114, 1927-1938 (Box 21, Folder 221)
  - Land Acquisition - Steingraber - Parcel 71 - 4-44-114 and 14-45-114, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 222)
  - Land Acquisition - Stilson - Parcel 72 - 5-44-114, 1929-1930 (Box 21, Folder 223)
  - Land Acquisition - Prather - Parcel 73 - 10-44-114, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 224)
  - Land Acquisition - Coffin - Parcel 74 - 12 and 22-44-114, 1928-1932, 1944 (Box 21, Folder 225)
  - Land Acquisition - Harold - Parcel 75 - 13-44-114, 1928, 1933-1934 (Box 21, Folder 226)
  - Land Acquisition - Ericsson - Parcel 76 - 14-44-114, 1929-1930 (Box 21, Folder 227)
  - Land Acquisition - Dietz - Parcel 77 - 17-44-114, 1930, 1932-1933 (Box 21, Folder 228)
  - Land Acquisition - Hogan-Miller - Parcel 77a - 19-44-114, 1929-1930, 1933, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 229)
  - Land Acquisition - Ericsson - Parcel 78 - 20-44-114, 1928-1930, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 230)
  - Land Acquisition - Cunningham - Parcel 79 - 21 and 23-44-114, 1928-1930, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 231)
  - Land Acquisition - Turner - Parcel 80 - 24 and 26-44-114, 1929-1936, 1941 (Box 22, Folder 232)
  - Land Acquisition - Hedrick - Parcel 81 - 25-44-114 and J and C-44-114, 1929-1931 (Box 22, Folder 233)
  - Land Acquisition - Schwabacher-Hedrick - Parcel 81a - J and C-44-115, 1929-1934, 1938, 1942 (Box 22, Folder 234)
  - Land Acquisition - Eynon - Parcel 82 - 27-44-144, 1930-1931 (Box 22, Folder 235)
  - Land Acquisition - Buckenroth - Parcel 83 - 28-44-114, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 236)
  - Land Acquisition - Eynon - Parcel 84 - F and G-44-114, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 237)
  - Land Acquisition - Myers - Parcel 85 - K-44-114, 1929-1930 (Box 22, Folder 238)
  - Land Acquisition - Ericsson - Parcel 86 - I and K-44-115, 1928-1931, 1945 (Box 22, Folder 239)
  - Land Acquisition - Winger - Parcel 87 - 5 and F-44-115, 1929, 1931 (Box 22, Folder 240)
  - Land Acquisition - Huff - Parcel 88 - E-44-115, 1929, 1931, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 241)
  - Land Acquisition - LePage - Parcel 88a - 6-44-115 and B-43-115, 1929-1930, 1932-1934 (Box 22, Folder 242)
  - Land Acquisition - Crandall - Parcel 89 - 1-44-116, 1929-1930 (Box 22, Folder 243)
  - Land Acquisition - Grace - Parcel 90 - 2-44-116, 1920-1930, 1933, 1935-1936 (Box 22, Folder 244)
  - Land Acquisition - Smith - Parcel 91 - 3-44-116, 1929-1930 (Box 23, Folder 245)
  - Land Acquisition - L. Smith - Parcel 92 - 4-44-116, 1929-1930, 1932, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 246)
  - Land Acquisition - Bark - Parcel 93 - 6-44-116, 1929-1930 (Box 23, Folder 247)
  - Land Acquisition - Richard - Parcel 94 - 9-44-116, 1929-1930 (Box 23, Folder 248)
  - Land Acquisition - Tracy - Parcel 95 - 1-45-112 and 6 and 8-45-113, 1928-1930 (Box 23, Folder 249)
  - Land Acquisition - Erwin - Parcel 96 - 2-45-112, 1928 (Box 23, Folder 250)
  - Land Acquisition - McKinstry - Parcel 97 - 2-45-112, 1928 (Box 23, Folder 251)
  - Land Acquisition - N. Smith - Parcel 98 - 5-45-113, 1928 (Box 23, Folder 252)
  - Land Acquisition - Coolidge - Parcel 99 - 12-45-113, 1928 (Box 23, Folder 253)
  - Land Acquisition - R. Smith - Parcel 100 - 13-45-113, 1928 (Box 23, Folder 254)
  - Land Acquisition - B. Smith - Parcel 101 - 17-45-113, 1928-1930 (Box 23, Folder 255)
  - Land Acquisition - E. Smith - Parcel 102 - 23-45-113, 1930-1931 (Box 23, Folder 256)
  - Land Acquisition - Christian - Parcel 103 - 1-45-114, 1928 (Box 23, Folder 257)
  - Land Acquisition - Scalley - Parcel 104 - 2-45-114, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 258)
  - Land Acquisition - Lozier - Parcel 107- 5-45-114, 1929, 1931 (Box 23, Folder 259)
  - Land Acquisition - Markham - Parcel 108 - 6-45-114, 1931-1932 (Box 23, Folder 260)
  - Land Acquisition - Sheffield - Parcel 109 - 7-45-114, 1928-1931 (Box 23, Folder 261)
  - Land Acquisition - Sheffield - Parcel 109 - 7-45-114, 1928-1931 (Box 23, Folder 262)
  - Land Acquisition - Jackson Lake Lodge - Parcel 109a, 1929-1932, 1936, 1940 (Box 23, Folder 263)
  - Land Acquisition - Whiteman (Grimmesy, Webb, Jackson Lake Lodge, Inc.) - Parcel 110 - 8-45-114, 1929-1933, 1935, 1940 (Box 24, Folder 264)
  - Land Acquisition - Snell - Parcel 112 - 9-45-114, 1931 (Box 24, Folder 265)
  - Land Acquisition - Hogan - Parcel 113 - 10-45-114, 1927-1933, 1935, 1941, 1943 (Box 24, Folder 266)
  - Land Acquisition - Chapline - Parcel 114 - 11-45-114, 1928 (Box 24, Folder 267)
  - Land Acquisition - Ferrin - Parcel 115 - 15-45-114, 1928 (Box 24, Folder 268)
  - Land Acquisition - Lozier - Parcel 116 - 16-45-114, 1927-1929, 1931, 1933-1934 (Box 24, Folder 269)
  - Land Acquisition - Graham - Parcel 117 - A-44-114, B-45-113 and C-45-114, 1929-1930 (Box 24, Folder 270)
  - Land Acquisition - Ferrin - Parcel 118 - 1-45-113, 1929 (Box 24, Folder 271)
  - Land Acquisition - Wilson - Parcel 119 - 1-46-114, 1929-1930 (Box 24, Folder 272)
  - Land Acquisition - Chapline (Spicer) - Parcel 120 - 12-45-114, 1930, 1932-1933 (Box 24, Folder 273)
  - Land Acquisition - Transfer of Property to Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. - Parcel 151a, 1942-1943, 1949, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 274)
  - Land Acquisition - Transfer of Property to Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. - Capener Appraisal - Parcel 155, 1940-1941 (Box 24, Folder 275)
  - Land Acquisition - Transfer of Property to Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. - Mayash and Yokel Appraisal - Parcel 156, 1945 (Box 25, Folder 276)
  - Land Acquisition - State (School) Land - Parcel 199, 1927-1931, 1933-1934, 1936, 1938-1939 (Box 25, Folder 277)
  - Land Acquisition - Neilson - Parcel 200 - 2-44-115, 1929 (Box 25, Folder 278)
  - Land Acquisition - Corse - Parcel 201 - 27 and 28-43-116, 1929, 1936-1937 (Box 25, Folder 279)
  - Land Acquisition - Lucas - Parcel 202 - A-43-116 and 5-44-116, 1929 (Box 25, Folder 280)
  - Land Acquisition - Scott - Parcel 203 - C-43-116, 1925-1926, 1929 (Box 25, Folder 281)
  - Land Acquisition - P. Smith - Parcel 204 - H-43-115, 1929 (Box 25, Folder 282)
  - Land Acquisition - Harold - Parcel 205 - D-44-114, 1929, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 283)
  - Land Acquisition - Wolff - Parcel 206 - B and 11-44-114, 1930 (Box 25, Folder 284)
  - Land Acquisition - Budge (Lundy) - Parcel 207 - A-43-115 and I and H-44-115, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 285)
  - Land Acquisition - Crandall - Parcel 208 - 1-44-116, 1929 (Box 25, Folder 286)
  - Land Acquisition - Richard - Parcel 209 - F and C-44-116, 1929 (Box 25, Folder 287)
  - Land Acquisition - Huff - Parcel 210 - 7-44-116, 1930 (Box 25, Folder 288)
  - Land Acquisition - Kent - Parcel 211 - 8-44-116, 1929-1930 (Box 25, Folder 289)
  - Land Acquisition - Chapline - Parcel 212 - A-45-114, 1929-1930 (Box 25, Folder 290)
- Teton Companies, 1930-1976; 2; 2.4 Cubic Feet 8 document cases
  Arrangement note
  This series is arranged to reflect corporate relationships. It begins with the Teton Investment Company and is followed by the Teton Lodge Company, the Teton Transportation Company, Jackson Lake Lodge, Inc., Grand Teton Lodge and Transportation Company, and Grand Teton Lodge Company.
  This series contains director's minutes, financial statements, and correspondence.
  - History of the Companies, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 291)
  - Company Reports, 1930, 1932, 1933 (Box 26, Folder 292)
  - Teton Investment Company - Board of Director's Minutes, 1930-1936, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 293)
  - Teton Investment Company - Directors and Officers of Teton Companies, 1933, 1935, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 294)
  - Teton Investment Company - Stockholder Lists, 1930, 1932-1933, 1935-1936 (Box 26, Folder 295)
  - Teton Investment Company - Stockholder's Minutes, 1930-1937 (Box 26, Folder 296)
  - Teton Investment Company - Correspondence, 1929-1936 (Box 26, Folder 297)
  - Teton Investment Company - Budget and Accounting - Receipts, 1930, 1933-1936 (Box 26, Folder 298)
  - Teton Investment Company - Treasury Department - Form 707 - Return of Capital-Stock Tax, 1935 (Box 26, Folder 299)
  - Teton Investment Company - Corporate Oaths of Office, 1930, 1933-1934, 1936 (Box 26, Folder 300)
  - Teton Lodge Company - Board of Director's Minutes, 1930-1936 (Box 26, Folder 301)
  - Teton Lodge Company - Stockholder's Minutes, 1932, 1935-1936 (Box 26, Folder 302)
  - Teton Lodge Company - Correspondence, 1929 (Box 26, Folder 303)
  - Teton Lodge Company - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 27, Folder 304)
  - Teton Lodge Company - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 27, Folder 305)
  - Teton Lodge Company - Correspondence, 1932-1936 (Box 27, Folder 306)
  - Teton Lodge Company - Correspondence - Daum and Larom, 1930-1931 (Box 27, Folder 307)
  - Teton Lodge Company (Box 27, Folder 308)
    McCarter Reconstruction Report, 1929 Rayburn, Monay and Brennan Operations Reports, 1930
  - Teton Lodge Company - "Existing Buildings Plat of Moran, Wyoming" (McCarter Map), 1929 (Box 27, Folder 309)
  - Teton Lodge Company - "Proposed Development at Moran, Wyoming" (McCarter Map), 1929 (Box 27, Folder 310)
  - Teton Lodge Company - Blueprint of Single Frame Cabins (McCarter), 1930 (Box 27, Folder 311)
  - Teton Lodge Company - Blueprint of Typical Bedstead (McCarter), 1929 (Box 27, Folder 312)
  - Teton Lodge Company - Financial Reports, 1929-1930 (Box 27, Folder 313)
  - Teton Lodge Company (Box 27, Folder 314)
    Lease Receipts, 1933-1934 Bank Statements, 1935
  - Teton Lodge Company (Box 27, Folder 315)
    Construction Account Receipts, 1929-1930 McCarter Expenses and Receipts, 1930
  - Teton Lodge Company - Treasury Department - Form 707 - Return of Capital-Stock Tax, 1935 (Box 27, Folder 316)
  - Teton Lodge Company - Fox Film Corporation Contract, 1930 (Box 28, Folder 317)
  - Teton Lodge Company - Publicity, 1930-1935, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 318)
  - Teton Transportation Company - Board of Director's Minutes, 1930-1934, 1936 (Box 28, Folder 319)
  - Teton Transportation Company - Stockholder's Minutes, 1932, 1935-1936 (Box 28, Folder 320)
  - Teton Transportation Company - Correspondence, 1929-March 1930 (Box 28, Folder 321)
  - Teton Transportation Company - Correspondence, April 1930-1936 (Box 28, Folder 322)
  - Teton Transportation Company - Financial Reports, 1930-1931 (Box 28, Folder 323)
  - Teton Transportation Company - Receipts, 1930-1936 (Box 28, Folder 324)
  - Teton Transportation Company - Annual License - Idaho, 1930, 1934-1935 (Box 28, Folder 325)
  - Teton Transportation Company - Schedule and Rates, 1932 (Box 28, Folder 326)
  - Teton Transportation Company - Treasury Department - Form 707 - Return of Capital-Stock Tax, 1935 (Box 28, Folder 327)
  - Teton Transportation Company - Oaths of Corporate Office, 1929-1936 (Box 28, Folder 328)
  - Jackson Lake Lodge, Inc. - Board of Directors Minutes, 1934, 1936 (Box 28, Folder 329)
  - Jackson Lake Lodge, Inc. - Correspondence, 1927, 1930, 1932 (Box 28, Folder 330)
  - Jackson Lake Lodge, Inc. - Financial Report, June 1931 (Box 28, Folder 331)
  - Jackson Lake Lodge, Inc. - Treasury Department - Form 707 - Return of Capital-Stock Tax, 1935 (Box 28, Folder 332)
  - Jackson Lake Lodge, Inc. - Publicity, 1931-1932, 1934, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 333)
  - Grand Teton Lodge and Transportation Company (Box 28, Folder 334)
    Board of Directors, 1946 Minutes, 1953
  - Grand Teton Lodge and Transportation Company (Box 28, Folder 335)
    Stockholder's List, 1937 Minutes, 1953
  - Grand Teton Lodge and Transportation Company - Jack Wentworth Correspondence, 1945-1947 (Box 28, Folder 336)
  - Grand Teton Lodge and Transportation Company - Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 29, Folder 337)
  - Grand Teton Lodge and Transportation Company - Correspondence, 1947-1969 (Box 29, Folder 338)
  - Grand Teton Lodge and Transportation Company - Financial Reports, 1945-1946, 1952-1956 (Box 29, Folder 339)
  - Grand Teton Lodge and Transportation Company - Budget and Accounting Correspondence, 1943, 1945-1946 (Box 29, Folder 340)
  - Grand Teton Lodge and Transportation Company - Daily Reporting Procedures, ca. 1947 (Box 29, Folder 341)
  - Grand Teton Lodge and Transportation Company - Budget and Accounting Reports, 1946, 1948-1949, 1951-1953 (Box 29, Folder 342)
  - Grand Teton Lodge and Transportation Company - Lease with Grand Teton National Park, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 343)
  - Grand Teton Lodge and Transportation Company - Research and Publicity, 1946, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 344)
  - Grand Teton Lodge and Transportation Company - Jackson Lake Lodge - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 345)
  - Grand Teton Lodge and Transportation Company - Jackson Lake Lodge - Correspondence, 1953-1955 (Box 30, Folder 346)
  - Grand Teton Lodge and Transportation Company - Jackson Lake Lodge - Construction Estimates, 1951-1954, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 347)
  - Grand Teton Lodge and Transportation Company - Jackson Lake Lodge - Contracts, 1953-1954 (Box 30, Folder 348)
  - Grand Teton Lodge and Transportation Company - Jackson Lake Lodge - Construction Reports, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 349)
  - Grand Teton Lodge and Transportation Company - Jackson Lake Lodge - Lobby Design, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 350)
  - Grand Teton Lodge and Transportation Company - Jackson Lake Lodge - Grand Opening, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 351)
  - Grand Teton Lodge and Transportation Company - Rate Schedules, 1954-1955 (Box 30, Folder 352)
  - Grand Teton Lodge and Transportation Company - Newspaper Articles, 1929, 1953-1956 (Box 30, Folder 353)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Board of Directors Minutes, 1956-1959 (Box 30, Folder 354)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Board of Directors Minutes, 1960-1975 (Box 31, Folder 355)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Board of Directors Minutes, 1960-1975 (Box 31, Folder 356)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Board of Directors Minutes, 1960-1975 (Box 31, Folder 357)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Budget and Accounting, 1956-1957 (Box 31, Folder 358)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Rate Schedules, 1956-1978 (Box 31, Folder 359)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Jenny Lake Lodge - Rehabilitation Plan, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 360)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Jenny Lake Lodge (Box 31, Folder 361)
    Menus, 1957-1958, 1976 History, 1976
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Jackson Lake Lodge - Merchandising Plan, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 362)
  - Chronology of Events, March 6, 1928-October 18, 1932 (Box 32, Folder 363)
  - Teton Investment Company - Articles of Incorporation, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 364)
  - Teton Investment Company - Financial Reports, 1930-1933 (Box 32, Folder 365)
  - Teton Investment Company - Corporation Report to Secretary of State of Utah, 1930-1931 (Box 32, Folder 366)
  - Teton Investment Company - Articles of Dissolution, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 367)
  - Teton Lodge Company - Articles of Incorporation, 1929-1930 (Box 32, Folder 368)
  - Teton Lodge Company (Box 32, Folder 369)
    Annual Report to Secretary of State of Wyoming, 1930-1935 Annual Report to Secretary of State of Utah, 1930
  - Teton Lodge Company - Don Miller Lease, 1932 (Box 32, Folder 370)
  - Teton Lodge Company - Articles of Dissolution, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 371)
  - Teton Transportation Company - Articles of Incorporation - Idaho and Wyoming, 1929-1930 (Box 32, Folder 372)
  - Teton Transportation Company - Public Service Commission Certificate, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 373)
  - Teton Transportation Company (Box 32, Folder 374)
    Corporation Report to Secretary of State of Wyoming, 1930-1935 Corporation Report to Secretary of State of Utah, 1930
  - Teton Transportation Company - Annual Statement of Foreign Corporations - Idaho, 1930-1931, 1933, 1935 (Box 32, Folder 375)
  - Teton Transportation Company - Articles of Dissolution, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 376)
  - Jackson Lake Lodge, Inc. (Box 32, Folder 377)
    Articles of Incorporation, 1926 Certificate of Purchase, 1926 Deed, 1927
  - Jackson Lake Lodge, Inc. - Annual Report to Secretary of State of Wyoming, 1932-1935 (Box 32, Folder 378)
  - Grand Teton Lodge and Transportation Company - F.C. Gillette Lease, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 379)
  - Grand Teton Lodge and Transportation Company - Water Rights, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 380)
  - Grand Teton Lodge and Transportation Company, 1951-1953 (Box 32, Folder 381)
    Budget and Accounting, Personnel
  - Cancelled Stock Book - Teton Investment Company (Box 33, Folder 0381A)
  - Cancelled Stock Book - Jackson Lake Lodge, Inc. (Box 33, Folder 0381B)
  - Cancelled Stock Book - Grand Teton Lodge and Transportation Company (Box 33, Folder 0381C)
- Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc., 1940-1981; 3; 10.8 Cubic Feet 28 document cases
  This series contains minutes, financial statements, correspondence, reports, maps, and blueprints. This is the largest series in the collection and, combined with the series for the Snake River Land Company, establishes the fifty-year continuity of the collection. The controversy surrounding the creation of Jackson Hole National Monument, the restoration of Menor's Ferry, property supervision, and the wildlife park are the largest topics in this series. Oversize material is grouped in Box 58.
  - Board of Trustees - Agendas Minutes and Correspondence, 1940-1959 (Box 34, Folder 382)
  - Board of Trustees - Agendas Minutes and Correspondence, 1940-1959 (Box 34, Folder 383)
  - Board of Trustees - Agendas Minutes and Correspondence, 1940-1959 (Box 34, Folder 384)
  - Board of Trustees - Agendas Minutes and Correspondence, 1960-1969 (Box 35, Folder 385)
  - Board of Trustees - Agendas Minutes and Correspondence, 1960-1969 (Box 35, Folder 386)
  - Board of Trustees - Agendas Minutes and Correspondence, 1960-1969 (Box 35, Folder 387)
  - Board of Trustees - Agendas Minutes and Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box 36, Folder 388)
  - Board of Trustees - Agendas Minutes and Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box 36, Folder 389)
  - Executive Committee (Finance Committee) Minutes, 1946-1971, 1974-1975 (Box 36, Folder 390)
  - Executive Committee (Finance Committee) Minutes, 1946-1971, 1974-1975 (Box 36, Folder 391)
  - Board of Trustees - Annual Financial Reports, 1942, 1945-1952, 1954-1963 (Box 37, Folder 392)
  - Financial Reports, 1942-1974 (Box 37, Folder 393)
  - Financial Reports, 1942-1974 (Box 37, Folder 394)
  - Budget and Accounting, 1941-1953 (Box 37, Folder 395)